no-more-calls.com 2017-11-26

# Privacy Policy | No More Calls!

No More Calls want to protect your privacy, so we do not collect any personally identifiable information on this website. This privacy policy explains our online information practices, including how we collect and use the information you may provide to us on our site, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

 **Information Collected**

The information you submit will be displayed to the public on the Website. Avoid posting your real name, email address, address or phone number within the post message.

We use cookies to personalize and enhance your experience on our sites. No personal information is gathered via the cookies. If you want to use our website without the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to change your cookie settings. This may affect certain Website functions..

 **Third Party Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Website. These companies may use cookies, pixel tags, or otherwise independently collect non-personally identifiable information from you and use this information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We do not control their collection and use of information.

 **Third Party  Links**

Our sites offer hyperlinks to other Websites which may have information policies and practices different from ours. We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or the content of any third party Websites. Once you’ve left our Web sites via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy  **

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Any modifications to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page.

 **Question About the Privacy Policy**

Questions should be emailed to us via our online [contact form](http://no-more-calls.com/contact-us/).
